ps3jailbreakdownloadfree.com 2019-06-17

# Privacy Policy | www.ps3jailbreakdownloadfree.com

Our website address is https://www.ps3jailbreakdownloadfree.com. Sirajul Huq is the M.D of this portal. This website is a blogging website on which we are regularly uploading new games with the download links for free, Technical assistance for the PS3, PS4 and other consoles like, Jailbreak, Game installation process, and many other useful details by which a user can save his/her time and cost. If, we say something about ps3jailbreakdownloadfree.com at a glance, that it’s a gaming place where all the things are totally free. We are also planning to sell new and old used video game consoles and accessories.

At www.ps3jailbreakdownloadfree.com, the privacy of our visitors is of extreme importance to us. This privacy policy document outlines the types of personal information is received and collected by www.ps3jailbreakdownloadfree.com and how it is used. This website adheres to Google AdSense Privacy policy & Terms and Conditions.

## What personal data we collect and why we collect it

We are using ultimate member word press plug-in. With the help of this plugin, a user can sign-up and sign-in. We only collect your username, first name, last name and email address for your convenience. The motto is only that we connect you and update you on our latest offers and news.

### Comments

When visitors leave comments on the site we collect the data shown in the comments form, and also the visitor’s IP address and browser user agent string to help spam detection.

An anonymized string created from your email address (also called a hash) may be provided to the Gravatar service to see if you are using it. The Gravatar service privacy policy is available here: https://automattic.com/privacy/. After approval of your comment, your profile picture is visible to the public in the context of your comment.

####  **Media**

If you upload images to the website, you should avoid uploading images with embedded location data (EXIF GPS) included. Visitors to the website can download and extract any location data from images on the website.

 **Contact Form**

 **Source:** Contact form 7. With the help of contact form 7 plugin, we require name and email address before submitting the contact form. We only use the contact form to service purposes, but we do not use the information submitted through them for marketing purposes.

#####  **Cookies**

If you leave a comment on our site you may opt-in to save your name, email address and website in cookies. These are for your convenience so that you do not have to fill in your details again when you leave another comment. These cookies will last for one year.

If you have an account and you log in to this site, we will set a temporary cookie to determine if your browser accepts cookies. This cookie contains no personal data and is discarded when you close your browser.  
When you log in, we will also set up several cookies to save your login information and your screen display choices. Login cookies last for two days, and screen options cookies last for a year. If you select “Remember Me”, your login will persist for two weeks. If you log out of your account, the login cookies will be removed.

If you edit or publish an article, an additional cookie will be saved in your browser. This cookie includes no personal data and simply indicates the post ID of the article you just edited. It expires after 1 day.

######  **Embedded content from other websites**

Articles on this site may include embedded content (e.g. videos, images, articles, etc.). Embedded content from other websites behaves in the exact same way as if the visitor has visited the other website.  
These websites may collect data about you, use cookies, embed additional third-party tracking, and monitor your interaction with that embedded content, including tracking your interaction with the embedded content if you have an account and are logged in to that website.

 **Analytics**

We are using google analytics to get check our visitor’s behaviour, activity and real-time users, but we are not sharing our analytics details with anyone.

 **Who we share your data with**

We respect our visitor and we know the value of your data. So, we have not shared any kind of our user data with any for any greed.

 **How long we retain your data**

If you leave a comment, the comment and its metadata are retained indefinitely. This is so we can recognize and approve any follow-up comments automatically instead of holding them in a moderation queue.

For users that register on our website (if any), we also store the personal information they provide in their user profile. All users can see, edit, or delete their personal information at any time (except they cannot change their username). Website administrators can also see and edit that information.

 **What rights you have over your data**

If you have an account on this site or have left comments, you can request to receive an exported file of the personal data we hold about you, including any data you have provided to us. You can also request that we erase any personal data we hold about you. This does not include any data we are obliged to keep for administrative, legal, or security purposes.

 **Where we send your data**

Visitor comments may be checked through an automated spam detection service.

 **Contact information**

 **Website:** https://www.ps3jailbreakdownloadfree.com  
**Facebook:** www.facebook.com/smartsktech  
**Twitter:** https://twitter.com/@smartsktech  
**Youtube:** https://www.youtube.com/channel/UCtIt88Bn9laXjCmUFwmqK9w

 **How we protect your data**

As we assure you on the above that we use Ultimate Member word press plug-in. It is very popular and also very secure plug-in which protects your data from theft.

 **What data breach procedures we have in place**

As we assured you of the above we are using most secured Ultimate Member word press plug-in. This plug-in will protect your data from the theft or any kind of violation. Further, if it happens then we strictly take action against the defaulters.

 **What third parties we receive data from**

No, we are not dealing with any third party for the data. We only use one signal which asks you for the push notification of new updates. It’s up to you subscribe it or not, one signal will not ask you for any data.

 **What automated decision making and/or profiling we do with user data**

We only use the user data for their benefit login account, give feedback on the post, and so on. But, we do not share our user data to anyone.

 **Log Files**

Like many other Web sites, www.ps3jailbreakdownloadfree.com makes use of log files. The information inside the log files includes internet protocol ( IP ) addresses, type of browser, Internet Service Provider ( ISP ), date/time stamp, referring/exit pages, and the number of clicks to analyze trends, administer the site, track user’s movement around the site, and gather demographic information. IP addresses and other such information are not linked to any information that is personally identifiable.

 **Cookies and Web Beacons**

www.ps3jailbreakdownloadfree.com does use cookies to store information about visitors preferences, record user-specific information on which pages the user access or visit, customize Web page content based on visitors browser type or other information that the visitor sends via their browser.

 **DoubleClick DART Cookie**

.:: Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on www.ps3jailbreakdownloadfree.com.  
.:: Google’s use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to users based on their visit to www.ps3jailbreakdownloadfree.com and other sites on the Internet.  
.:: Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy at the following URL – http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html

Some of our advertising partners may use cookies and web beacons on our site. Our advertising partners include …  
Google Adsense

These third-party ad servers or ad networks use technology to the advertisements and links that appear on www.ps3jailbreakdownloadfree.com send directly to your browsers. They automatically receive your IP address when this occurs. Other technologies ( such as cookies, JavaScript, or Web Beacons ) may also be used by the third-party ad networks to measure the effectiveness of their advertisements and/or to personalize the advertising content that you see.

www.ps3jailbreakdownloadfree.com has no access to or control over these cookies that are used by third-party advertisers.

You should consult the respective privacy policies of these, third-party ad servers for more detailed information on their practices as well as for instructions about how to opt-out of certain practices. www.ps3jailbreakdownloadfree.com’s privacy policy does not apply to, and we cannot control the activities of, such other advertisers or websites.

If you wish to disable cookies, you may do so through your individual browser options. More detailed information about cookie management with specific web browsers can be found at the browsers’ respective websites.
